<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aydin Mercan</title>
    <link>http://mercan.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aydin Mercan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://mercan.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://mercan.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mercan.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>I am Aydin Mercan (/ˈaɪdɪn merdʒan/), a sophomore CEng student at TOBB ETU. I am interested in security, cryptography and hardware description but I aim to share knowledge I stumble on from a broad of topics includings interests such as mathematics.
Name I have several legal variations of my name depending on where you ask me. However, Jaiden with any pronoun is fine by me.
This page will be expanded some time :p</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://mercan.dev/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mercan.dev/contact/</guid>
      <description>E-Mail   Primary: aydin [at] mercan [dot] dev
  Backup: aydinmercandev [at] gmail [dot] com
  Please prefer plain-text e-mail.
  I do not use PGP for e-mail.
  Signal   Contact me at plus nine zero five three two six five three two eight five seven
  Keep in mind that I currently reside in UTC+3 and expect answers accordingly.
  Misc   LinkedIn</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity Keys</title>
      <link>http://mercan.dev/keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mercan.dev/keys/</guid>
      <description>Age  age1hqwq0yp3stqxqmwe79vl2m3fv438xpealxsd7ehdeg2mhkvgqshqfgee7x  Minisign/Signify  RWQK6C+naHpMTM59i6ajFKD8JXYpPE2lDN+GKWR/2xLNrEJ5GP5nWfoa  PGP Don&amp;rsquo;t use PGP for securing communications.
 It is bad and outdated as a platform. It refuses to follow proper development practices. It is a gun that automatically points to your gun for no benefit.  However it is the only way to sign git commits. As a result I will have a single sign-only key that will not be uploaded to a keypool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Library</title>
      <link>http://mercan.dev/library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mercan.dev/library/</guid>
      <description>This includes papers, articles and (mostly) books. It is currently horribly incomplete.
Planned  [REREAD] Mano, M. Morris. Ciletti, Michael D. Digital Design with an Introduction to Verilog HDL, VHDL and SystemVerilog (Sixth Edition). Silverman, Joseph H. A Friendly Introduction to Number Theory. Silverman, Joseph H. The Arithmetic of Elliptic Curves. Howell, Larry L. Compliant Mechanisms. Friedman, Daniel P. Felleisen, Matthias. The Little Schemer. Friedman, Daniel P. Felleisen, Matthias. The Seasoned Schemer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Equipment</title>
      <link>http://mercan.dev/equipment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mercan.dev/equipment/</guid>
      <description>Everyday Software   Tarsnap
  Wireguard
 They just work. Can recommend.    Binary Ninja
 Personally my favourite reverse engineering/analysis software.    Kitty
 Not only its GPU accelerated (like Alacritty), it has font per unicode region support and ligatures.    KiCad, Godot, Ardour, Blender and Krita
 I am not a professional in these areas so I just use powerful but open software that does the job for me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
